Guide to the Edwin Patrick Kilroe Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: Index of Volumes I-XVIII
  - Bostwick, Arthur E Page 583
  - Botsford, Prof. George Page 529
  - Bowker, R.R. & Company Pages 859 | 901
  - Boyle, Edward F. Pages 642 | 643
  - Boyle, John A. Pages 528 | 531 | 533 | 670 | 673
  - Bradford, Charles S. Pages 45a-b | 730
  - Bradley, J.S. Jr. Pages 814 | 828
  - Brady, Charles Page 813
  - Breen, Matthew P. Pages 48 | 519
  - Brennermann, E.H. Page 583
  - Brentano's, Inc. Pages 532 | 583 | 637 | 639 | 640 | 642 | 643 | 673 | 686 | 698 | 701a | 709 | 710 | 726 | 727 | 729 | 759 | 760 | 770 | 774 | 785 | 786 | 796 | 807 | 812 | 814 | 828 | 829 | 830 | 841 | 842 | 843 | 847 | 848 | 855 | 898 | 899 | 900 | 901 | 902 | 913-921 | 926 | 935
  - Breslau Book Store Page 730
  - Brewer, L.P. Page 880
  - Bridges, C.H. (Major General) In file No. 1507
  - Briggs, William Page 529
  - Brigham, Clarence, S. Pages 9-26 | 528 | 530 | 531 | 532 | 533 | 593 | 636 | 638 | 642 | 643 | 660 | 686 | 697b | 729 | 730 | 738 | 759 | 774 | 796 | 783 | 815 | 828 | 858 | 899
  - Brinker, Josiah H Pages 639 | 686 | 689 | 697b | 721
  - British Emprie, Chamber of Commerce in U.S. Pages 789 | 798
  - Broderick, Robert E. Page 661
  - Brooklyn Eagle Pages 644 | 697 | 717
  - Brooklyn Public Library Pages 528 | 552 | 527 | 611
  - Brothers of the Book Page 643
  - Brown, Alexander M. Pages 637 | 640 | 642 | 698 | 807
  - Brown & Brown Pages 531 | 533 | 632
  - Brown, Charles H. Pages 528 | 552 | 643
  - Brown, Henry Collins Pages 815 | 827
  - Brown (John Carter) Library Pages 194 | 204 | 639 | 641 | 721 | 729 | 730 | 760
  - Brown, Martin B. & Co. Pages 516a | 528 | 533 | 632
  - Brown University Pages 533 | 637 | 667
  - Browne, Stewart Page 828
  - Bruce, Leslie C. Page 827
  - Brush, William D. Page 532
  - Bryan, Vincent Page 642
  - Bryan, William J. Pages 533 | 583
  - Brylawki, Fulton Pages 858 | 901
  - Brylawki, Fulton In file No. 1506
  - Buck, B.F. Pages 533 | 634
  - Buckner, Emroy R. Page 730
  - Bucks Co. (Penn.) Historical Society Pages 57-60 | 733
  - Budd "Back Number" Pages 528 | 532
  - Budd, Henry Pages 786 | 796
  - Buildings, Bureau of Page 813
  - Bullet, M.M. Page 730
  - Bullock, William Pages 815 | 828
  - Bulmor, Benjamin Pages 531 | 614 | 642
  - Bureau for American Ideals Page 816
  - Bureau of Municipal Research Page 793
  - Burleson, Hugh L. Pages 528 | 530 | 566
  - Burleson, S. Page 642
  - Burrage, Champlin Pages 639 | 641 | 636 | 729 | 730 | 760
  - Burrelle Clipping Bureau Page 532
  - Bush, Wilson Doe Page 583
  - Butler, Albert Page 531
  - Byoir, Carl Page 583
  - Cabaen, Francis Von A. Page 731
  - Cadby, James W. Pages 534 | 537 | 538 | 539 | 543 | 546 | 612 | 624 | 645 | 655
  - Caddington, A.M. Pages 770 | 773
  - Cademus Book Shop Pages 692 | 702 | 731 | 763 | 796
  - Callahan, Joseph M. Page 815
  - Calloway, Edward B. Page 537
  - Campbell Studio Page 810
  - Campbell, William J. Pages 786 | 811 | 862 | 900 | 934
  - Cannon, C.L. Pages 786 | 796
  - Cantor, Maurice Page 830
  - Cantrill, James Page 540
  - Caplin, Stephen Page 773
  - Caraway, T.H. Page 796
  - Caraway, T.H. In file No. 1217
  - Carlson, Arthur B. Page 815
  - Carnegie Institute, Washington, D.C. Pages 45b | 62-66a
  - Carnegie Library Pages 736 | 738
  - Carroll's Book Store Page 545
  - Carter, Charles D. Pages 731 | 734
  - "Cartoon," Chicago, IL Pages 67-78 | 645
  - Cassidy, Lewis C. Pages 815 | 830
  - Catholic Builders of the Nation Page 812
  - Catholic World Page 925
  - Catholic Writers Guild Page 799
  - Catt, Walling Page 740
  - Census Bureau Page 516b
  - Century Club Page 824
  - Chadbourne, Thomas M. Page 543
  - Chamberlain, George E. Page 647
  - Chambers, D.L. In file No. 1155
  - Chandler, Walter M. Page 796
  - Chapin, Howard M. Pages 383 | 384 | 386 | 387 | 389-392 | 534 | 535 | 538 | 539 | 540 | 541 | 591 | 622 | 634 | 644 | 665 | 692 | 731 | 734 | 776 | 777 | 796
  - Chard, Standish Page 140b
  - Chenault, Nettie B. Pages 235-236
  - Cheney, H.A. Pages 877 | 879 | 900 | 909
  - Chillicothe Public Library Pages 600 | 645
  - Christian Monitor Page 830
  - Christian Science Publishing Society Page 821
  - Citizen Pub. Co. Pages 543 | 544
  - City Court of the City of New York Page 826
  - Clark, A.S. Pages 69 | 70 | 70b | 542
  - Saxe, Martin Pages 885 | 911
  - Clark, Arthur H.Co. Pages 516b | 534 | 536 | 537 | 538 | 539 | 540 | 541 | 543 | 611 | 624 | 645 | 646 | 647 | 665 | 692 | 723 | 726 | 731 | 734 | 765 | 786 | 796
  - Clark, Champ Page 567
  - Clark, Evans Page 815
  - Clark, G.T. Page 773
  - Cobb, M.B. Page 139
  - Cochran, John J. Page 796
  - Cochrane, J.W. Page 548
  - Cockran, William Bourke Pages 71 | 75 | 518 | 540 | 541
  - Cohalan, Daniel F. Page 76
  - Colier, James William Page 647
  - Collector (The) Page 883
  - Collier, James A. Page 647
  - Colonial Families of America Page 882
  - Columbia University Pages 2 | 36 | 42 | 77-100 | 329a | 783 | 793 | 796 | 797 | 799 | 812
  - Columbia University Alumni Council Page 542
  - Columbia University Athletic Association Page 817
  - Columbia University Book Store Pages 539 | 542 | 692 | 783 | 796 | 797 | 812
  - Columbia University Library Page 818
  - Columbia University Press Pages 817 | 818 | 830 | 844 | 862 | 900 | 931
  - Columbia University Pub. Co. (Donehue's Magazine) Pages 70b | 101
  - Columbia Spectator Pages 539 | 596
  - Colson, Fred D. Pages 542 | 580
  - Commerce & Labor, Department of Pages 76a | 516b
  - Committee for the Adoption of the Constitution Page 665
  - Commonweal (The) Page 924
  - Compton, George B. Page 542
  - Connelly, D.H. Page 787
  - Congressional Library Pages 538 | 539 | 545 | 560 | 654 | 664 | 665 | 666 | 691 | 697c | 697e | 736 | 738
  - Connecticut Magazine Page 534
  - Conor, R.D.W. Pages 341 | 383
  - Consular Service Pages 734 | 740
  - Cook, John H. Pages 537 | 546
  - Copeland, Royal S. Pages 866 | 900
  - Copyright Office Pages 76b | 516b
  - Corell, Philip Pages 76b | 110a
  - Cormely, J. Williard Page 678
  - Cosmopolitan Magazine Page 102
  - Court of Common Pleas, No. 5 Page 823
  - Cox, William Page 830
  - Craig, Locke Page 647
  - Crane, H.W. Page 634
  - Crane, R.D. Pages 815 | 830
  - Craven, L.R. Pages 103 | 104
  - Cresson, Sarah Page 535
  - Crewe, Roxford Page 540
  - Criminal Court of Appeals, Oklahoma City Page 816
  - Crimmins, Jonathon D. Pages 537 | 539
  - Croker, Richard Page 537
  - Croll, Edward E. Page 789
  - Cronin, Richard M. Pages 764 | 796
  - Cronin, Richard M. In file No. 1217
  - Crowell, Thomas Y Co. Pages 540 | 632 | 634
  - Cuddeback, S.M. (Minnisink Valley Historical Society) Pages 105 | 108
  - Culkin, Charles W. Pages 538 | 543 | 665 | 796
  - Cullop, William A Pages 540 | 665
  - Curley, James M. Pages 534 | 543 | 545 | 796
  - Current Literature Pub. Co. Pages 109 | 110a
  - Current Opinion Pages 110 | 110a | 535
  - Currey, John F. Association Page 671
  - Curtis, Charles T. Pages 1-42a | 110 | 535 | 537 | 543 | 610 | 614 | 615 | 645 | 731 | 734
  - Curtis, John T. Pages 538 | 539
  - Cushing (J.S.) Co. Page 110b
  - Cushman, Captain Norman F. In file No. 1507
  - Cypress Hill Cemetery In file No. 1507
  - Daily Mail Page 548
  - Daily Telegraph Page 606
  - Daniels, Josephus Page 771
  - Darlington, Dr. Thomas Pages 546 | 547 | 548 | 797 | 866
  - Darlington, Dr. Thomas In file No. 1507
  - Darlington, Dr. Thomas In file No. 1155
  - Darnalt, Edwin M., M.D. Page 849
  - Davenport, James S. Pages 816 | 831
  - Davies, J. Clarence Pages 546 | 549
  - Davis Book Store Pages 111 | 663
  - Davis, Edwin L. In file No. 1217
  - Davis, Ewin L. Pages 797 | 831
  - Davis, H.H. Pages 548 | 608
  - Davis, John A. Page 866
  - Davis, Julian H. Pages 650 | 651
  - Davis, Mary L. Pages 569 | 732 | 740
  - Davis, O.W. Page 770
  - Davis, R. Pages 548 | 663 | 698 | 707
  - Deane, Ruthven (Ruth) Pages 649 | 651 | 697 | 864 | 865 | 903
  - Decker, Porl D. Pages 647 | 652
  - DeForest, Robert W. Page 16
  - Deiches, Maurice Page 648
  - DeLaney, E.A. Page 549
  - Delaven, Samuel E. Page 649
  - Delaware State Library Page 112
  - Democratic County Committee Page 824
  - Democratic National Committee Pages 870 | 929
  - Democratic State Committee Page 824
  - Department of Printed Books, British Museum Pages 825 | 827
  - Department of State Pages 634 | 740
  - Department of the Interior, U.S. Pages 818 | 823
  - DeWitt (Tompkins County, NY) Historical Society Page 152
  - De Wolfe & Fiske Co. Page 849
  - Dickstein, Samuel Page 797
  - Dickstein, Samuel In file No. 1217
  - Dies, Martin Page 732
  - Dillingham (G.W.) Co. Page 546
  - Dixie Book-Shop Page 549
  - Dixon, J.K. Pages 113-114
  - Dobson, George Page 831
  - Dodd, Mead & Co. Pages 546 | 629
  - Dodge, Cleveland E. Page 831
  - Doherty, Agnes A. Page 549
  - Doherty, Anna I. Page 115
  - Domestic and Foreign Missionary Society of P.E. Church Pages 531 | 566
  - Donahue, D.D. Pages 816 | 830 | 831 | 849
  - Donahoe's Magazine Pages 101 | 116
  - Donelin, Mary C. Page 854
  - Donelin, Mary C. In file No. 1507
  - Donnelly (R.R.) & Sons Co. Pages 116a-c
  - "Dorms" (The) Page 651
  - Dorm's Book Store Page 610
  - Dorsey, W. Pages 646 | 697
  - Dotten, F. Pages 546 | 549
  - Doubleday, Doran & Co. Pages 871 | 903
  - Doubleday, Page & Co. Pages 116c | 548
  - Douglass, Francis P. Page 732
  - Dowling, E. Page 866
  - Downing, Daniel J. Page 816
  - Drewry, P.H. In file No. 1217
  - Drucker & Co. Pages 608 | 623 | 763 | 810 | 811
  - Drumm, Eugene A. Page 831
  - Drumm, Stella M. Page 732
  - Dugro, P. Henry Page 549
  - Dulligan, James F. Pages 866 | 903
  - Duncan, Margaret L. Page 775
  - Dunn, J.J. Page 652
  - Dunn, Rev. John Page 670
  - Dutton, E.P. & Co. Pages 546 | 629 | 648 | 649 | 650 | 651 | 652 | 653 | 663 | 668 | 697 | 703 | 710 | 724 | 732 | 768 | 772
  - Durand, E. Dana Pages 437-449
  - Durkin, Joseph A. Pages 866 | 903
  - Dutton, E.P. & Co. Page 903
  - Eagle, Joe Henry Page 562
  - Eamies, Wilberforce Pages 645 | 786
  - Eastmond, John Pages 831 | 867 | 903
  - Eclectic Magazine Page 117
  - Economy Magazine Exchange Pages 645 | 719
  - Eddy, A.H. Pages 779 | 797
  - Edelstein, Minnie Page 697f
  - Edes, Henry H. Pages 118 | 119
  - Educational Pub. Co. Page 125
  - Educational Review Pages 121-121a | 550 | 562
  - Edwards (Gus) Pub. Co. Pages 122 | 645
  - Einbigler, Benjamin F. Pages 121a | 645 | 656 | 696 | 728
  - Eisenberg, Leo M. Page 740
  - Ely, Edward A. and/or Warren S. Pages 59 | 60 | 123 | 124 | 550 | 562 | 633 | 733
  - Emerson, Frank W. Pages 654 | 696
  - Enoch, Pratt Free Library (Baltimore, MD) Pages 420 | 421
  - Erb, Frnak C. Pages 646 | 696 | 793 | 812
  - Erickson Co. Page 733
  - Evans, Clara Therese Pages 793 | 797
  - Evening Post Page 562
  - Farnum, J.L. Pages 238-245 | 264a-d | 538 | 545 | 569 | 654 | 664 | 666 | 697e | 738 | 770 | 816
  - Farnum, Jessica L. In file No. 1507
  - Farquharson, J.W. Page 870
  - Fay, Professor Bernard Pages 869 | 869A | 883 | 903 | 905
  - Feigl, Fred Pages 126 | 435a | 831 | 868 | 905
  - Feigl, George Page 773
  - Ferree, Barre Pages 551 | 577 | 664
  - Ferrero, (Prof.) Guglielmo Page 125
  - Ferris, Scott Pages 652 | 797
  - Ferris, Scott In file No. 1217
  - Fickele, Charles Pages 577 | 634
  - Figaro Page 551
  - Finder & Wibel Pages 702 | 705
  - Fingeroth, Elizabeth Page 812
  - Fippinger, W.F. Page 600
  - Flaherty, Frank B. Pages 733 | 773
  - Flood, H.D. Page 577
  - Folsom, Joseph F. Page 582
  - Ford, Worthington C. Pages 435a | 646 | 691
  - Fordham University Page 813
  - Forrest, Jay W. Page 551
  - Fortier, Alcee Pages 265 | 266
  - Forty-Second St. Studio Pages 638 | 701a | 707 | 710 | 711 | 723 | 761 | 770 | 809 | 811 | 844
  - Forum Magazine Page 128
  - Foster, Hugh M. Page 551
  - Foster, Warren W. Pages 129 | 519
  - Fowke, Gerard Pages 125 | 577
  - Fowler, H.A. Page 664
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan Page 735
  - Fraser, A.N. In file No. 1507
  - Free, Marguerite Page 540
  - Freeman, S.B. Co. Page 551
  - Freidberg, Robert Page 733
  - Freschi, John I. Page 733
  - Fuller, Mrs. Claud E. Pages 817 | 831
  - Funk & Wagnalls Co. Pages 435a | 577 | 628 | 831
  - Furman, Dorothy Page 733
  - Fusion Committee of 1917 Page 730
  - Galbreath, C.B. Page 346
  - Gallivan, James A. Pages 552 | 626 | 797
  - Gallivan, James A. In file No. 1217
  - Galvin, John F. Pages 130-131 | 553 | 567 | 632 | 641 | 656 | 728 | 797 | 817 | 831 | 870 | 904 | 905
  - Gard, Warren Page 777
  - Gardiner, Asa Bird Pages 132-134 | 521 | 553
  - Garrett, Finis J. Pages 777 | 797
  - Geddes, Donald P. Page 862
  - Geffin, Elizabeth Page 777
  - General Society of Mechanics and Tradesmen Pages 581 | 826 | 904
  - George, Henry, Jr. Pages 135-136
  - Georgia Historical Society Page 137
  - Gerard, Henri Pages 553 | 555
  - Gerard, James W. Page 870
  - Gerhardt & Co. Pages 140 | 555 | 567 | 622
  - Gerould, J.T. Page 555
  - Gessford, J.G. Page 621
  - Gettler, John M. Pages 728 | 765
  - Gibbon, Amiel Pages 553 | 554 | 567
  - Gibbon, Marion Pages 140a | 516b
  - Gibboney, Stuart G. Pages 553 | 567
  - Gibbs, Joseph F. Pages 140a-b | 516b
  - Gilbert, B.E. Page 774
  - Gilpatrick, Walter J. Pages 553 | 567 | 626
  - Gilroy, Thomas F. Pages 141 | 142
  - Glynn, Martin H. Page 555
  - Goddard, M. Page 580
  - Goff, John R. Page 143
  - Gold, Samuel M. Page 870
  - Goldfogle, Henry M. Page 797
  - Goldman, Mayer C. Page 656
  - Goldsmith Bros. Pages 721 | 762 | 805 | 811 | 844 | 938
  - Good Citizen Page 740
  - Goodkind Publicity Co. Pages 769 | 810
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop Pages 144-146a | 567 | 623 | 687 | 702 | 870 | 871 | 904
  - Gookin, Edward L. Pages 817 | 831
  - Gorhman Press Page 855
  - Gorhman Press In file No. 1155
  - Gossage, Ralph E. Page 817
  - Grady (Miss) (Senator Thomas F. Grady) Page 147
  - Grant, Donald E. Pages 652 | 653 | 658 | 668 | 697 | 724
  - Grant, Edward J. Page 817
  - Graves, Charles Page 566
  - Gray, Arthur F. Page 789
  - Greathouse, Charles A. Pages 863 | 905
  - Green, Charles R. Pages 817 | 831
  - Greenberg, David S. Page 728
  - Greene, Clay M. Page 150
  - Greene, L.G. Pages 636 | 658
  - Greenwood Cemetery In file No. 1507
  - Greenwood, M.M., Jr. Page 151
  - Gregory, Percivall H. Page 663
  - Griffus, William E. Page 152
  - Guernsey, Rocellus S. Pages 146a | 153 | 552 | 553 | 567 | 610 | 625
  - Guild, Georgiana Pages 656 | 687
  - Gunton's Magazine Page 154
  - Guy, Charles L. Pages 817 | 831
  - Hackatt, G. In file No. 1507
  - Hafner, Alfred Page 834
  - Hagerly, W.J. Page 905
  - Haines, Benjamin F. Page 556
  - Hall, Edward Hagaman Pages 657 | 684
  - Hall, James S. Pages 871 | 904 | 927
  - Hall, Lillian A. Pages 817 | 818
  - Hamill, James A. Pages 155 | 578
  - Hamilton, Oscar W. Pages 658 | 659
  - Hancock, La Touche Pages 647 | 659 | 673 | 724
  - Harburger, Leopold W. Pages 634 | 657
  - Harlem Home News Page 904
  - Harper Bros. Pages 146a | 156-157 | 517 | 561
  - Harris, Daniel M. Page 659
  - Harris, Ralph S. Page 560
  - Harrison, Pat Page 797
  - Harrison, Pat In file No. 1217
  - Hartog, Alfred Pages 783 | 797 | 817 | 818 | 834
  - Harvard College Library Pages 817 | 818 | 825
  - Harvard Theatre Collection Pages 834 | 872 | 892
  - Harvey, Oscar J. Pages 158-162
  - Harwood, Van Ness Page 786
  - Hauke, C.F. Page 818
  - Hawes, Harry B. Page 797
  - Hawes, Harry B. In file No. 1217
  - Hawley, Edna Page 352
  - Haycroft, Mary C. Pages 228-229
  - Hayden, Horace E. Pages 501 | 513
  - Hayes, Alice Sheridan Pages 882 | 907
  - Hayes, James Pages 894 | 907
  - Hayes, Joseph H. Page 743
  - Hays, W.H. Page 557
  - Heartmann, Charles Frederick Pages 557 | 561 | 620 | 624 | 625 | 657 | 690 | 698 | 708 | 710
  - Heaton, Augustus G. Pages 687 | 690 | 725 | 769
  - Heflin, J. Thomas Page 561
  - Hegel, E.H. Pages 642 | 643
  - Heinemann, William Page 618
  - Heitmuller Art Co. Pages 163 | 167 | 516c | 558 | 560 | 578 | 610 | 657 | 684 | 723
  - Heitmuller, Arthur Pages 159a-c | 163-167 | 657
  - Hellyer, Anna Page 797
  - Henkels, Stanley V. Pages 659 | 702 | 765
  - Henle, James Pages 894 | 904
  - Hennsler, Arthur F. Page 168
  - Henry, Robert L. Pages 560 | 561
  - Herbert, F. Hugh Pages 789 | 797 | 818 | 834
  - Herzenberg, S.K. Pages 561 | 578 | 657
  - Hicks, Frederick C. Pages 89-92 | 818
  - Hildebrand, William A. Pages 159c | 160 | 169 | 186a | 516c | 559 | 560 | 561 | 578 | 610 | 616 | 644 657 | 658 | 659 | 684 | 689 | 714 | 715 | 716 | 717 | 718 | 722 | 723 | 724 | 768 | 781 | 790 | 791 | 792 | 795 | 797 | 800-804 | 810 | 818 | 819 | 820 | 832 | 845 | 849 | 850 | 851 | 852 | 871 | 872 | 904 | 927
  - Hildebrandt, C.Q. Page 654
  - Hill, Mr. (Photographer) Page 187
  - Hill, Frank P. Pages 557 | 611
  - Hill, Walter M. Pages 687 | 743
  - Hillyer, W.O. Page 793
  - Hines, George Page 352a
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania Pages 561 | 589 | 736 | 738 | 740 | 775
  - History of Tammany Hall Pages 816 | 818
  - Hitchcock, Frederick H. Page 834
  - Hitchcock, Frederick H. In file No. 1155
  - Hodge, F.W. Page 560
  - Hoey, James J. Pages 820 | 821 | 832 | 872 | 873 | 904
  - Hoffman, E.S. Page 904
  - Holden, J.A. Pages 557 | 859
  - Holly, Willis Pages 778 | 781 | 787 | 797 | 820 | 821 | 833 | 834 | 852 | 874 | 904 | 905 | 907
  - Holmes, John Haynes (Rev.) Page 905
  - Holt, Elsa R. Page 871
  - Holt, Henry & Co. Pages 561 | 684
  - Holt, Roland Page 834
  - Homeletic Review Pages 188-189
  - Honest Ballet Association Page 561
  - Hopper, Jonathon J. Pages 560 | 561
  - Hornaday, W.T. Page 697f
  - Hosbach, G.T. Page 660
  - Hosbach, T.A. Page 687
  - Hotchkiss, Thomas Pages 557 | 560 | 561 | 578 | 646 | 687 | 821 | 834
  - Hotovetsky, Alexander Page 557
  - Hough, Henry Battle Page 651
  - Houghton Mifflin & Co. Pages 561 | 628
  - Howard, W. Schley Page 743
  - Howe, Alfred F. Pages 687 | 797
  - Howe, Stanley Page 743
  - Hucker, J.W. Page 562
  - Huddleston, George Page 797
  - Huddleston, George In file No. 1217
  - Hudson River Book Concern Page 528
  - Hughes, Rev. Daniel J. In file No. 1507
  - Hulbert, G. Murray Pages 647 | 660 | 687
  - Hull, Prof. Charles H. Page 743
  - Hulse, Robert J. Page 930
  - Hunt, Edward L. (Rev.) Page 927
  - Hunt, Gaillard Page 246
  - Hyden, Horace F. Page 658
  - Hyer, Richard Pages 787 | 797
  - Hymans, Leonard & Co. Page 557
  - Imhof, Hannah V. Pages 770 | 834 | 875
  - Independent (The) Pages 190a | 643
  - Independent (Periodical) Pages 190 | 563 | 602
  - Indian Affairs Page 834
  - Ingraham, J. Van Ness Page 247
  - International Pages 563 | 602
  - International Magazine Co. Page 611
  - Interior, Department of Page 516b
  - Iowa, State University Page 643
  - Jacobson, Edna L. In file No. 1507
  - James, Alice R. Pages 735 | 763
  - James, B.O. Page 654
  - James T. White & Co. Page 821
  - Jameson, J. Franklin Pages 61-66 | 563 | 593
  - Jergegan, Marcus W. Pages 191-193 | 563
  - John Carter Brown Library Pages 194-204
  - Johnson, Charles F. Pages 552 | 626
  - Johnson, E.W. Pages 205-210 | 552 | 564 | 613 | 614 | 615 | 616 | 617 | 618 | 622 | 623 | 772 | 773 | 785 | 798 | 809 | 810 | 812
  - Johnson, Herbert A. Page 821
  - Johnson, Mrs. H.C. Pages 739 | 767
  - Johnson, John Barent Page 739
  - Johnson, Joseph J. Pages 785 | 798
  - Johnson, Mrs. William Allen Pages 739 | 767
  - Johnson, J. Stoddard Pages 211-215 | 611
  - Jones & Co. (D.L.) Page 625
  - Jones Library Page 817
  - Jones, Morgan Pages 785 | 798
  - Jordan, John W. Pages 363 | 369a | 552 | 561 | 563 | 736 | 740
  - Jordan, Miss Page 325
  - Kahn, Julius Page 737
  - Kain, F.B. Pages 821 | 834
  - Kaplan, Abraham Pages 787 | 907
  - Kaufman, E.R. Pages 216 | 219
  - Keating, Edward Page 737
  - Keep, Austin B. Pages 220 | 230a | 528 | 532 | 565 | 602 | 611 | 616 | 617 | 737 | 770 | 785 | 798 | 834 | 907
  - Keep, C.H. Page 821
  - Kelby, Robert H. Pages 582 | 597 | 770
  - Kelleher Page 737
  - Keller, Frank Page 737
  - Keller, (McAllister-Keller Co.) Page 766
  - Kelley, John W.A. Pages 876 | 907
  - Kellicott, Gertrude S. Page 567
  - Kelly, (Mrs.) John Pages 221 | 519
  - Kemp, E.L. Pages 222-225
  - Kempner, Otto E. Pages 226 | 517
  - Kennerly, Mitchel Pages 566 | 625 | 628
  - Kenney, Lawrence Page 566
  - Kenney, M.F. Page 566
  - Kent, Henry W. Pages 230a | 299 | 567 | 577
  - Kentucky State Library Pages 227-229
  - Kerwin, H.L. Page 775
  - Kessler, G.W. Pages 561 | 566
  - Kiernan, Adrian T. Pages 565 | 793
  - King, E. Howard Page 737
  - King, Mrs. Horatio C. Page 737
  - Kirchgraber, Earl Page 565
  - Kitchen, Claude Page 798
  - Klein, H.H. Pages 785 | 798
  - Knickerbocker Press Pages 566 | 567
  - Knopf, Alfred A. Page 628
  - Knox, Raymond C. Page 93
  - Koenig, Samuel Page 567
  - Koopman, H.L. Pages 51-56
  - Krafft, H.F. Pages 821 | 835
  - Krauss, L. & Son Pages 566 | 567
  - Photostat of Deed: Tammany Hall Property, 28 March 1928 (Box 30)
  - Kunz, George Pages 627 | 834
  - Labor, Department of Page 230
  - Ladd, Miel Morrow Co. Pages 578 | 579 | 667 | 722
  - Ladd, P.L. Page 568
  - Lafferty, Mrs. W.T. Pages 735 | 741 | 773
  - Lake, Stuart N. Pages 877 | 906 | 907
  - Lampson, George G. Page 668
  - Land (John) Co. Page 773
  - Landauer, Bella C. Pages 821 | 835
  - Langenheim, F.D. Page 580
  - Langtry, Albert P. Page 654
  - Lawby, William E. Page 906
  - Lazarus, B. Pages 230-231
  - Lazelle, W.H. Page 725
  - Ledger (N.Y.) Page 676
  - Le Mirror (Editor of) Page 656
  - Lee, John Thomas Pages 654 | 660 | 688 | 692
  - Leet Bros. Pages 625 | 646 | 656 | 667
  - Leet, Grant Page 656
  - Lemcke, E.J. Pages 542 | 622
  - Lemcke & Buechner Page 730a
  - Lent, Tilda Page 786
  - Leonard, John W. Corp. Page 845
  - Leslie, Charles J. Page 568
  - Leslie Judge Co. Pages 233 | 233a | 568 | 579
  - Leslie's Weekly Pages 2322 | 568
  - Levy, Eugene Page 549
  - Levy Type Co. Page 656
  - Lewis Historical Publication Co. Pages 568 | 656 | 666
  - Lewis, James Hamilton Pages 568 | 569 | 773
  - Lexington Book Co. Page 234
  - Lexington Book Shop Pages 516c | 579
  - Lexington (KY) Public Library Pages 235-236 | 730
  - Libby & Co. Pages 237 | 666 | 707
  - Library of Congress Pages 238-264 | 264a-b | 538 | 539 | 545 | 560 | 568 | 569 | 597 | 614 | 626 | 736 | 738 | 816 | 835 | 929
  - Library of Congress In file No. 1507
  - Lippincott, Oliver Page 569
  - Livingston, Robert E. Page 836
  - Livingston, R.M. Page 824
  - Lloyd, A. Page 741
  - Lloyd Studio Pages 734 | 765
  - Lockwood, Charles C. Page 666
  - Lombard, Herbert Edwin Pages 636 | 638 | 656
  - London Times Pages 546 | 549 | 606
  - Lonergan, Augustine Page 798
  - Lonergan, Augustine In file No. 1217
  - Long, Theodore In file No. 1507
  - Longmans, Green & Co. Pages 876 | 878 | 906 | 938
  - Lorimer, George Horace Page 821
  - Loughman, M.F. Page 821
  - Louisiana Historical Society Pages 127 | 265-266
  - Louisville Courier Page 267
  - Lowdermilk, W.H. & Co. Pages 822 | 835 | 852
  - Lucas, P.A. Pages 660 | 688 | 690 | 697a | 740
  - Luce, Robert L. Pages 667 | 822 | 835 | 852
  - Lull, Robert W. Pages 903 | 906 | 932 | 936
  - Lydenberry, H.M. Pages 582 | 668 | 740 | 769
  - Lynn, Wanhope Pages 568 | 579 | 666 | 667 | 741
  - Lyons, Anna E. Pages 822 | 836
  - McAdoo, William A. Pages 574 | 576 | 661
  - McAllister-Keller Co. Pages 701a | 766 | 808 | 924
  - McAlpin, Charles W. Page 268
  - McAndrews, Thomas Pages 906 | 909
  - McIntyre, James Pages 881 | 906 | 909 | 917 | 919 | 923
  - McAuliffe & Booth Pages 836 | 845
  - McAvoy, Thomas F. Page 579
  - McBain, Howard Lee Page 836
  - McBride Nast & Co. Pages 571 | 574 | 575 | 576
  - McCabe (Mr.) Pages 385 | 388
  - McCarthy, Charles Pages 572 | 574
  - McCarthy, William D.J. Page 808
  - McClean, Robert B. Page 582
  - McClure, A.C. & Co. Page 688
  - McClure's Magazine Page 628
  - McClure (S.S.) Publishing Co. Page 269
  - McClure, S.S. Pages 575 | 581
  - McCrystal, Elizabeth Page 798